Guide to the New York State College of Home Economics records, 1875-1979
Cornell University, New York State College of Home Economics records,
- Series I. Administration and Personnel
  - Non-Professional Staff
    - Corser, N. Eugenia; Courchene, Anna-May; Cox, Ethel Cecilia; Crook, Mrs. Royal D.; Cunningham, Mrs. Margaret C.; Curtis, Elizabeth, 1930-1952 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Dailey, Laura G.; Daino, Teresa; Daland, Jane; Daniels, Mrs. Mary; Dann, Stephen; Darrah, Mrs. Wanda; Davidson, Virginia; Davis, Edna, 1926-1947 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Davis, Mrs. Ruth; De Benham, Mrs. Mary Alden; De Bye, Marion; Dedlow, Mrs. Louise; Delgado, Charles; DeLong, Luella; Dennis, Beulah May; De Prey, Alberie; DeSantis, Mrs. Anita; Devenpeck, Mrs. H. S, 1927-1946 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Dietzen, Dorothy May; Dietzen, Gretchen; Donaldson, Ada Belle; Donnelly, Mathilde O.; Dougherty, Mrs. Ruth; Dowe, Doris; Driscoll, Anna; Driscoll-, Elizabeth; Durbon, Dorothy; Dutcher, Willena, 1921-1951 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Ebersol, Mrs. Marjorie; Edinger, Mrs. P. L.; Elliott, Margaret G.; Ellsworth, Annie Merrill, 1923-1953 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Fabbricatore, Catherine S. (deceased); Farley, Stella; Farling, Helen P.; Finneran, Mary C.; Fish, Mrs. Mildred Wadley; Fisher, Evelyn; Flynn, Eileen Marie; Francis, Mrs. Helen; Freeman, Herbert; French, Mrs. Eva; Fudge, Emily Louise, 1919-1951 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Gaiser, Mrs. Celia; Gallagher, Eleanor Marie; Gallimore, Madge; Gaynor, Evelyn M.; Gehshan, Mrs. Henrietta Burgott; Geller, Sarah; Getman, Mrs. Marguerite, 1918-1952 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Giles, Isabelle; Glaeser, Marion; Gluck, Rhena; Goldbas, Mrs. Beverly Stern; Goldsmith, Mrs. Lucy; Gooding, Velma; Gragg, Mrs. Dorothy; Graver, Dona, 1933-1943 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Green, Mrs. Mary J.; Greig, Blodwen; Greig, Jean; Gulling, Mrs. Ruth Osborn; Gunn, Julia R, 1921-1950 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Hadley, Charles; Hagin, Bernice; Hagin, Mrs. Evelyn; Hakes, Vivian J.; Halstead, Mrs. Anna - includes photograph; Hammond, M. C.; Harford, Ida T., 1918-1951 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Hartley, Clinton; Haskins, Marion; Hayes, Elizabeth; Hayflich, Kate G.; Healy, Lolita; Henderson, James E.; Henderson, Lavern V.; Henighen, Kathryn M, 1918-1942 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Heron, Mary Catherine; Hershey, Mrs. Donald; Hess, Mrs. Florence; Hinkelman, Dorothy; Hipolit, Mrs. Jeannette M.; Holt, Margaret, 1942-1950 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Homma, Mrs. Isao; Hoppe, Mrs. Margaret - includes photograph; Horstman, Honora; Horton, Mrs. Vera; Hosmer, Emily; Howe, Ann; Howe, Ruth M.; Howes, Louise A, 1939-1952 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Hoover, Margaret; Hubbell, Irene Dean; Hubel, Dorothy; Hughes, Lillian Virginia; Hull, Marjorie; Humphreys, Lydia; Hunn, Anna E.; Huntington, Ellen; Hurlbutt, Edith M. Fenner; Hutchinson, Lois V, 1915-1952 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Ingersoll, Mary G.; Inscho, Dorothy; Jack, Elizabeth Jane; Jackson, Joyce, 1918-1951 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Jacobs, Mrs. Marguerite M.; Jansen, Ruby; Johannessen, Patricia Martin; Johnson, Mrs. Irma Y.; Johnson, Seth D.; Jones, Blanche; Jones, Mrs. Clarence, 1927-1950 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Jones, Ethel J.; Jones, Frances M.; Junkin, Mrs. Elsie; Kane, Catherine; Kayko, Mrs. Ingeborg; Kellogg, Mrs. G.; Kelly, Lovina L.; Kercher, Lydia Z.; Kerns, Mrs. Stella, 1918-1951 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - King, Mrs. Helen E.; Knapp, Claude; Koch, Mrs. Nan; Kockenmeister, E. C.; Kogan, Sally; Kopman, Alta; Kornfeld, Florence M.; Kutz, Mrs. Anne, 1925-1952 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Lane, Anna E.; Lanning, Mrs. Nancy Louise; Lapp, Isabel; Larsen, Mrs. Helen L.; Laubengayer, E. Dorothy; Lee, Margaret; Lennox, Mrs. Eva, 1929-1946 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Lenox, Mrs. Theresa; Leonard, Edwin, Lewis, Dick; Lewis, Gertrude; Linke, Mrs. Esther; Lisenring, Margaret, Little, Mabel; Long, Francis; Lund, Mrs. Ethel; Lynch, Helen; Lyon, Helen, 1921-1948 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Madison, Winifred L.; Magill, Diana; Mann, Mrs. Winifred; Manning, Dorothy; Manos, Mary G.; Mapes, Anna; Marion, Mrs. Doris Grace; Marion, Wanda; Martin, Eugene Joseph; Massey, Mrs. Elizabeth, 1935-1952 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Matthews, Mrs. Eleanor; Matthews, Mrs. Eileen; Mattice, M. C.; Mattuci, Elvera; Maynard, Dorothea Matteson; Mazza, Angeline; MacBain, Marjorie; McCandless, Nancy Philips; McCarthy, Mary Catherine; McClintock, Mrs. Evelyn F.; McClure, Florence, 1923-1951 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - McCracken, Kermit King; McCredy, Mrs. Jeannette E.; McCusker; Mrs. Joan Louise; McDaniels, Mary A.; McFerren, Margaret G.; McGraw, Mayme L.; McIlroy, Annie; McSkimming, Isabelle, 1946-1949 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Medlin, Clara Cuthbertson; Merdes, Mrs. Norma Wardle; Merriman, Ruth J.; Merritt, Ruth Stacey; Messinger, Mrs. Constance N, 1927-1949 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Miller, Lido; Minor, Carol; Mirantz, Mrs. Arline C.; Morehouse, Beverly Lynch; Morrow, Anne; Moskowitz, Mrs. Blanche T.; Moulton, Priscilla; Mundy, Elbert; Murphy, Arthur W, 1921-1949 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Murphy, Mrs. Eleanor Curtis (Sturges) - includes photograph; Myers, Mrs. Joan; Nardi, Clara; Nedrow, E. Paul; Newman, Elsie M.; Newton, Naomi; Nichols, Morey, 1942-1951 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Nobles, Mrs. Betty; Nolan, Anna; Nulle, Rachel Worthen; Nurmi, Elizabeth; Oehrle, Paula; Olson, Ethel; Overacker, Mrs. George; Overacker, George B, 1919-1950 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Packard, Mrs. Elizabeth; Parker, George W, 1921-1936 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Parsons, Mrs. Elsa; Paul, Thelma M.; Pearson, Mrs. Dorothy; Peiser, Mrs. Edith - includes photograph, 1941-1949 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Perez, Mrs. Mary Harrison; Pendleton, Mrs. Ann B.; Perkins, Alice W, 1933-1949 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Phillips, Mrs. Dorothy E.; Pierson, Blanche E. Martin; Pope, Vieno Pertula; Pratt, Mrs. Marian; Presswitz, Mrs. Marqery S, 1928-1947 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Probert, Dorothy; Probert, Dorothy Ann; Pullan, Edythe; Randolph, Mabel; Rathbun, Mrs. Alberta, 1920-1952 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Reed, Lucille Coggshall; Reed, Madeline Church; Reese, Irene Dowe; Reisman, Mrs. Leorita; Reslet, Frances Williams (Mrs.); Reulein, Pauline Babcock, 1933-1958 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Rezelman, Reyer; Rhea, Mrs. Flavia Wagner; Richards, Mrs. Joyce; Roach, Jacqueline C.; Robson, Mina, 1943-1949 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Roe, Sara; Rogers, Ruth S. Tilley; Ronto, Rose C.; Root, Hazel C.; Roskelly, Mrs. Helen; Ross, Evelyn; Ross, Mrs. Grace; Rosser, Mrs. Annetta; Roth, Evelyn, 1922-1951 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Royce, Mary G.; Ruane, Mary Rita; Rundle, Eleanor J.; Russell, Claribel; Russo, Mrs. Erna B.; Ryan, Bernadine F.; Ryan, Mrs. Bessie Belle - includes photograph, 1918-1947 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Sabella, Mrs. Marjorie; Sailor, Mrs. Sara B.; Saltsman, Anna; Sampel, Ruth D.; Sampson, Mrs. Marie; Sandman, Mrs. E. M. - includes photograph; Schaffer, Amelia; Schmehl, Mrs. Elizabeth P.; Schmidt, Fatanitza Louise - includes photograph; Schmutz, Mrs. LaRue; Schoenfeld, Mrs. Edith Martin; Schubert, Mrs. Ruth D., 1922-1951 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Scudamore, Margaret; Seeholzer, Dorothy; Shelley, Mrs. Charline L.; Sheppard, Lillian E.; Short, Mrs. Madeline, 1927-1948 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Sigler, Rita; Sinski, Anthony; Slater, Mildred; Smirlock, Mrs. Doris; Smith, Barbara; Smith, Hilda Agnes; Smith, Mrs. Katherine M.; Smithcovs, Mrs. Martha; Somers, Mrs. Beulah; Stanzinao, Mrs. Helen M, 1929-1949 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Stevens, Dorothy, B. (Buckley); Stewart, Marjorie, J.; St. John, Ruth N.; Stimson, Mary Bradley; Stockholm, Gladys; Stocking, Mrs. Harriet, 1929-1951 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Stoehr, Mrs. Aida; Storey, Mrs. Marian - includes photo graph; Storey, Mary; Stout, Mrs. J. C.: Strasburg, Mrs. Dorothy E.; Stritzinger, Gustave; Stritzinger, Mina, 1938-1948 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Stromberg, Mrs. Jean; Sturges, Sally Lou; Swanson, Mrs. Mildred; Swartley, Mrs. Elizabeth; Swartwood, Mrs. Lena; Sweatland, George; Swisher, Mrs. Marjorie; Sykes, Clara, 1919-1950 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Tack, Betty; Takce, Ethel - includes photograph; Tate, Mrs.; Taylor, Mrs. Louise; Tefft, Mrs. Jean; Thilly, Margaret; Thomas, Eleanor; Thomas, Ella Anderson; Thompson, Bertha (Mrs.), 1935-1951 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Thorne, Dorothy L.; Tittle, Mrs. Marcia; Todd, Dorothy; Todd, Mrs. Emily B.; Tomidy, Veronica Lorayne; Tompkins, Mrs. Flossie; Treleaven, Nellie; Tucker, Mildred; Tudi, Lela; Turner, Mrs. Mildred Edith; Tyree, Helen Agnes, 1926-1952 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Underwood, Irene J.; Van Natta, Doris; Volze, Eleanor C., Wardwell, Mrs. Lorena; Watros, Glenn; Watros, Vida Steen burgh; Watt, Martha W.; Weibly, Janice Mae; Weil, Frances M.; Weinberger, Irene; Weissbecker, Alice J., 1929-1949 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Welch, Cora; Welch, Mrs. Doris; Welch, Sarah; Westbrook, Mrs. Edna; Westlake, Harriet; Wetherbee, Phyllis Jeanne; Whipple, Diane (Barkdoll); Whitaker, Louise; Whitcraft, Marie, 1929-1951 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Whitford, Dora; Whitford, June; White, Annie M.; Wilcox, Barbara A.; Wilhelm, Bernice Louise - includes photograph; Wilkinson, Helen; Wilkinson, Mary - includes photograph; Wilkinson, Virginia Ruth; Williams, Barbara, 1927-1952 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Williams, Frances; Williams, Margery E. Ufford; Williamson, Edith Getman; Wilmot, Thomas; Wilson, Annabeth; Wolff, Helene C.; Wolff, Martha L.; Wood, Rachel, 1921-1947 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Woodruff, Jeanette; Woods, Mrs. Mary Ellen; Woods, Shirley M.D.; Wooley, Hope; Wright, Mrs. Lucille; Wyman, Mrs. Florence - includes photograph; Yager, Joseph; Zapf, Florence M, 1918-1952 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Employment of students at College, 1913-1921 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Employment of students, alumni, non-students; reference and recommendation, 1906-1921 (Box 9, Folder 7-12)
    - Employment of students, alumni, non-students; reference and recommendation, including brochures of the American Missionary Association and the National Service Commission of the Congregational Churches of America, 1911-1918 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - College Faculty and Staff
    - Staff correspondence: individual household, industrial and personal problems, 1908-1921 (Box 9, Folder 14-20)
    - Staff Civil Service Report, 1930-1931 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Study of Faculty Ranks, 1944; 1947 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Study of Degrees held by Faculty, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Staff attendance at professional and scientific meetings, 1938-1940 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - School visiting by College faculty members, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Home visiting by staff members, 1938-1942 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Data on faculty and staff, 1913-1947 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Stenographic and Clerical Services
    - Stenographic service studies, 1937, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Stenographic service, 1943-1944, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Mimeograph and multilithing reports, 1940-1947 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Committees, Lists of, 1932-1942 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Standing Committees of the College, 1927-1946 (Box 9, Folder 32-33)
    - Spafford Study- Foods and Nutrition, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 34-41)
    - Spafford Study - Household Art, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Spafford Study - Textiles and Clothing, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Spafford Study - Home Economics Education, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Spafford Study - General, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Spafford Study - Economics of the Household, 1936-1937 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Discussion group on General Education, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Evaluations of the College
    - Study of undergraduate teaching and checklist on other work, 1939-1940 (Box 9, Folder 48-49)
    - Memorandum on Certain Aspects of Administration in Cornell University, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Legal matters - Legislation: correspondence, 1908-1921 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Federal laws - Smith-Lever Act, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Federal laws - Relation of federal cooperative extension employees to agricultural organizations, 1922-1938 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Federal laws - Capper-Ketcham Act, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Federal laws - Hope-Flannagan Bill, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - State laws - Laws of New York State concerning Extension, 1924-1930 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - State laws - College of Home Economics legislation of New York State Senate and Assembly, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - State laws - Amendments to New York Vehicle and Traffic Law, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Local laws - legal problems of the department, 1910-1911 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Miscellaneous administrative materials - administrative calendar of College, 1943-1962 (Box 9, Folder 60-61)
    - Miscellaneous administrative materials - college objectives, preliminary work, 1932-1942 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Financial matters - Budgets, 1912-1935 (Box 9, Folder 63-66)
    - Financial matters - Budgets, 1912-1935 (Box 10, Folder 1-6)
    - Financial matters - Budget publications, 1935-1952 (Box 10, Folder 7-10)
    - Revised Budqet, 1945-1946 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Budgets, 1949-1954 (Box 10, Folder 12-13)
    - Miscellaneous budgetary matters, 1908-1966 (Box 10, Folder 14-15)
    - Emergency budget, 1941-1943 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Transfer of bookkeeping to Roberts Business office, 1943-07 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Budget - Acceleration, 1942-1944 (Box 10, Folder 18-19)
    - Budget - Bonuses, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Special state defense funds, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous financial and budgetary materials, 1949-1959 (Box 10, Folder 22-26)
    - Research budget information, 1949-1959 (Box 10, Folder 27-31)
  - Records of the College of Home Economics Placement Office, Including Alumni Files
    - College Alumni/Personnel records, 1920-1949
    - Correspondence concerning graduates of the College of Home Economics not being eligible to become members of the American Association of University Women, 1937-1946 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Admissions interviews, 1934-1940 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Position descriptions, 1931-1934 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Abbott, Sarah, 1918-1928 (Box 60, Folder 4)
      Class of 1918
    - Abbuhl, Elizabeth, 1917-1931 (Box 60, Folder 5)
      Married name Boardman
      Class of 1917
    - Acomb, Helen, 1917-1922 (Box 60, Folder 6)
      Married name Pfafflin
      Class of 1920
    - Adams, Gladys, 1926 (Box 60, Folder 7)
      Class of 1928
    - Adams, Helen, 1917-1941 (Box 60, Folder 8)
      Married name Chapin
    - Adelson, Sadye, 1935 (Box 60, Folder 9)
      Class of 1924
    - Adsit, Sybil, 1966-1968 (Box 60, Folder 10)
      Married name Paddock
      Class of 1935
    - Aker, Frances, 1933-1935 (Box 60, Folder 11)
      Married name Girard
      Class of 1936
    - Alberding, Freda, 1937-1949 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Albertson, Mary, 1918-1920 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Alderman, Edna, 1916 (Box 60, Folder 14)
      Married name Wolfe
      Class of 1914
    - Allen, Laura, 1923-1962 (Box 60, Folder 15)
      Married name Preston
    - Allis, Elizabeth, 1919-1937 (Box 60, Folder 16)
      Married name Ferguson
      Class of 1919
    - Allyn, Helen, 1939-1941 (Box 60, Folder 17)
      Married name Jackson
      Class of 1929
    - Alward, Elizabeth, 1918-1952 (Box 60, Folder 18)
      Married name Kilbourne
    - Anderson, Alfrida, 1937-1958 (Box 60, Folder 19)
      Married name Hewitt
    - Anderson, June, 1934-1962 (Box 60, Folder 20)
      Married name Robertson
      Class of 1934
    - Andrews, Gertrude, 1931 (Box 60, Folder 21)
      Married name Small
      Class of 1931
    - Anton, Beatrice, 1944 (Box 60, Folder 22)
      Married name Saltford
      Class of 1933
    - Arant, Anamerle, 1930-1948 (Box 60, Folder 23)
      Graduate student
    - Armstrong, Harriet, 1924 (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Arnold, Mary Miller, 1930 (Box 60, Folder 25)
      Married name Mueller
    - Aronson, Grace, 1932 (Box 60, Folder 26)
      Married name Gordon
    - Aronson, Julia, 1917-1949 (Box 60, Folder 27)
      Married name Dushkin
    - Ashcroft, Ethelwyn, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - Austin, Hester, 1916 (Box 60, Folder 29)
      Married name Botsford
      Class of 1916
    - Avery, Alice, 1932-1944 (Box 60, Folder 30)
      Married name Guest
      Class of 1932
    - Ayer, Mary Ellen, 1936-1939 (Box 60, Folder 31)
      Married name Davison
    - Babcock, Olivia, 1937-1940 (Box 60, Folder 32)
    - Badger, Constance, 1916-1928 (Box 60, Folder 33)
      Married name Brooks
    - Baker, Helen, 1937-1943 (Box 60, Folder 34)
      Married name Hopkins
      Class of 1930
    - Baldwin, Mabel, 1917-1939 (Box 60, Folder 35)
      Married name Erskine
    - Ball, Leda Thala, 1939 (Box 60, Folder 36)
      Married name Fuller
    - Banks, Elizabeth, 1914-1917 (Box 60, Folder 37)
      Married name Nix
    - Barker, Jane, 1937-1939 (Box 60, Folder 38)
      Married name Pringle
    - Barrett, Winnie, 1921-1924 (Box 60, Folder 39)
      Married name Emmick
    - Bassett, Iris, 1917 (Box 60, Folder 40)
      Married name Coville
    - Bassett, Octavia, 1940 (Box 60, Folder 41)
    - Bates, Esther, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 42)
      Married name Montague
    - Bates, Gertrude, 1919-1921 (Box 60, Folder 43)
    - Beadle, Ruth, 1930-1942 (Box 60, Folder 44)
    - Bean, Iona, 1948-1965 (Box 60, Folder 45)
      Married name Hart
    - Beard, Reba, 1918-1932 (Box 60, Folder 46)
      Married name Snarr
    - Beardsley, Edna, 1916-1928 (Box 60, Folder 47)
    - Bechtel, Elaine, 1933-1957 (Box 60, Folder 48)
    - Beck, Florence, 1922-1934 (Box 60, Folder 49)
      Class of 1921
    - Becker, Charlotte, 1935-1958 (Box 60, Folder 50)
      Married name Hunt
    - Becker, Elna, 1918-1947 (Box 60, Folder 51)
      Class of 1915
    - Becker, Ernestine, 1918-1937 (Box 60, Folder 52)
    - Becker, Florence, 1924-1934 (Box 60, Folder 53)
      Married name McCrary
      Class of 1923
    - Beecher, Lena, 1919 (Box 60, Folder 54)
      Married name Greenman
    - Bennett, Alice, 1936-1938 (Box 60, Folder 55)
      Married name Planck
    - Bennett, Grace, 1917-1961 (Box 60, Folder 56)
      Married name Landergren
      Class of 1911
    - Bergholtz, Hilma, 1915-1917 (Box 60, Folder 57)
    - Berkeley, Florence, 1919-1921 (Box 60, Folder 58)
      Married name Bailey
    - Bethke, Lucille, 1939-1945 (Box 60, Folder 59)
      Married name Bateman
    - Betts, Bertha, 1916-1922 (Box 60, Folder 60)
      Married name Reisner
    - Bibik, Sophie, 1940 (Box 60, Folder 61)
      Married name Archer
    - Billings, Beatrice, 1933 (Box 60, Folder 62)
    - Birge, Ruth, 1937 (Box 60, Folder 63)
      Married name Schuleen
    - Bjorkman, Elsie, 1938 (Box 60, Folder 64)
      Married name Carpenter
    - Bjornason, May, 1935 (Box 60, Folder 65)
      Married name Neel
    - Black, Hortense, 1925-1945 (Box 60, Folder 66)
      Married name Pratt
    - Blinn, Alice, 1917-1944 (Box 60, Folder 67)
    - Blodgett, Mary, 1919-1931 (Box 60, Folder 68)
    - Bly, Winifred, 1923-1925 (Box 60, Folder 69)
      Married name Robson
    - Bohnet, Ruth Laura, 1925-1927 (Box 60, Folder 70)
      Married name Keller
      Class of 1927
    - Boies, Ruth, 1931 (Box 60, Folder 71)
      Married name Comstock
    - Boldt, Anita, 1942 (Box 60, Folder 72)
      Married name Von Bleicken
    - Bonenfant, Virginia, no date (Box 60, Folder 73)
      Married name McGrath
    - Bonenfant, Virginia, no date (Box 60, Folder 74)
    - Booker, Nancy Lee, 1925-1928 (Box 60, Folder 75)
      Married name Morey
      M.S. 1936, PhD 1921
    - Booole, Helen, 1919-1928 (Box 60, Folder 76)
      Married name Scallon
    - Boone, Fannie, 1916-1938 (Box 60, Folder 77)
      Married name Carney
    - Booth, Elizabeth, 1934 (Box 60, Folder 78)
      Married name Miller
    - Borst, Dorothy, 1933-1935 (Box 60, Folder 79)
      Married name MacFeiggan
    - Boyer, Beatrice, 1926 (Box 60, Folder 80)
      Married name Beattie
    - Boyesen, Constance, 1931 (Box 60, Folder 81)
      Married name Winter
    - Boynton, Alice, 1918-1927 (Box 60, Folder 82)
      Married name Vaughn
    - Boynton, Pearl, 1923-1928 (Box 60, Folder 83)
      Married name Balderston
      Class of 1913
    - Brace, Esther, 11923 (Box 60, Folder 84)
    - Borace, Ruth, 1917-1928 (Box 60, Folder 85)
      Married name Knapp
    - Brady, Amy Catherine, 1927-1938 (Box 60, Folder 86)
      Married name Dwelly
    - Bratley, Hazel, 1933-1934 (Box 60, Folder 87)
      M.S. 1927
    - Brauner, Lillian, 1931-1932 (Box 60, Folder 88)
      Married name Schultz
    - Bretsch, Gladys, 1924 (Box 60, Folder 89)
      Married name Odell
    - Bretsch, Marion, 1932 (Box 60, Folder 90)
      Married names Burbank and Nixon
    - Brewster, Alice, 1917-1946 (Box 60, Folder 91)
      Married name Porter
    - Bright, Jean, 1929 (Box 60, Folder 92)
      Married name Waller
    - Brigden, Doris, 1941-1956 (Box 60, Folder 93)
      Married name Medsger
      Class of 1937
    - Brill, Achsah, 1935 (Box 60, Folder 94)
      Married name Taylor
    - Brinkerhoff, Grace, 1927 (Box 60, Folder 95)
      Married name Fisk
    - Bristol, Anna, 1917 (Box 60, Folder 96)
      Married name Hall
    - Bristol, Grace, 1916-1931 (Box 60, Folder 97)
      Married name Cross
    - Brock, Dorothy, 1936-1944 (Box 60, Folder 98)
      Married name Hanlon
    - Broderick, Ruth, 1934-1943 (Box 60, Folder 99)
      Married name Harris
    - Brooks, Irene, 1916-1919 (Box 60, Folder 100)
      Married name Funk
    - Brown, Doris, 1932-1939 (Box 60, Folder 101)
      Married name Hodge
    - Brown, Gladys, 1929-1956 (Box 60, Folder 102)
    - Brown, Kathryn, 1943 (Box 60, Folder 103)
      Married name Apple
    - Brown, Marilyn, 1943 (Box 60, Folder 104)
      Married name Wansan
    - Brown, Rhea, no date (Box 60, Folder 105)
    - Browning, Clara, 1912-1920 (Box 60, Folder 106)
      Married name Goodman
      Class of 1912
    - Brundidge, Violet, 1921-1941 (Box 60, Folder 107)
      Married name Scheifele
    - Brush, Dorothy, 1934 (Box 60, Folder 108)
      Married name Spengler
    - Brush, Edna, 1915-1931 (Box 60, Folder 109)
      Married name Brady and Robbins
    - Buck, Edna, 1923-1926 (Box 60, Folder 110)
      Married name Jewett
    - Bugden, Doris, 1933-1942 (Box 60, Folder 111)
      Married name Blackwell
    - Bull, Helen, 1926-1970 (Box 60, Folder 112)
      Married name Vandervort
      Class of 1926
    - Burbank, Lucia, 1914-1916 (Box 60, Folder 113)
      Married name Bennett
    - Burgess, Elizabeth, 1932 (Box 60, Folder 114)
      Married name Benedict
    - Burke, Clara, 1928-1932 (Box 60, Folder 115)
      Married name Doubleday
    - Burns, Frances, 1940-1943 (Box 60, Folder 116)
      Married name LaFarr
    - Burr, Marjorie, 1928-1957 (Box 60, Folder 117)
    - Burritt, Helen, 1933-1939 (Box 60, Folder 118)
      Married name Latiff
    - Burt, Ruth, 1945 (Box 60, Folder 119)
      Maiden name Wallenwein
    - Burts, Marian, 1938-1940 (Box 60, Folder 120)
      Married name Williams
    - Button, Dorothy, 1918-1921 (Box 60, Folder 121)
      Married name Ryder
    - Buttrick, Helen, 1935-1937 (Box 60, Folder 122)
      Married name Whitney
    - Byrne, Gladys, 1920-1923 (Box 60, Folder 123)
    - Calhoun, Marie, 1931-1939 (Box 60, Folder 124)
      Married name Post
    - Campbell, Elva, 1927-1929 (Box 60, Folder 125)
    - Campbell, Louise, 1940-1950 (Box 60, Folder 126)
    - Campbell, Margaret, 1922-1944 (Box 60, Folder 127)
      Married name Shepard
    - Canby, Barbara, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 128)
    - Carle, Phyllis, 1933 (Box 60, Folder 129)
    - Carman, Roth, 1935-1940 (Box 60, Folder 130)
      Married name Lane
    - Carrick, Stephens, 1916-1918 (Box 60, Folder 131)
    - Carson, Ethel, 1924 (Box 60, Folder 132)
    - Case, Virginia, 1929 (Box 60, Folder 133)
      Married name Stevens
    - Caster, Bethel, 1936-1956 (Box 60, Folder 134)
    - Cattelain, Martha, 1932-1943 (Box 60, Folder 135)